Guide to the Vassar College Biographical Files, 1872-2023
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
Vassar College Biographical Files
1872-2023
Vassar College
50 cubic feet (80 boxes)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
Clippings, biographical information forms, news releases, memoranda, pamphlets, correspondence, photographs, book jackets, and articles. pertaining to the lives and careers of faculty, staff, administrators, trustees, and presidents of the college, as well as alumnae/i and other individuals with a siginificant relation to the development of the college.
Scope and Content Note
Clippings, biographical information forms, news releases, memoranda, pamphlets, correspondence, photographs, book jackets, articles, and other items pertaining to the lives and careers of faculty, staff, administrators, trustees, and presidents, as well as alumnae/i and other individuals with a siginificant relation to the development of the college.
Organized alphabetically.
Access
This collection is open for research according to the
regulations of the Vassar College Archives and Special Collections Library
without any additional restrictions.
Related Materials
There is a card file on early faculty and staff that may contain additional biographical information. For additional information, please contact the Archives and Special Collections Library staff.
Subject Headings
Organizations:
Vassar College--Alumni and alumnae; Vassar College--Faculty; Vassar College. Board of Trustees; Vassar College--Employees; Vassar College--Public relations
Subjects:
Authors; Women--Education; Women's colleges--New York (State)--Poughkeepsie; Women college teachers
Document Types:
Clippings; Correspondence; Photographs; Reports
VCL Categories:
Miscellaneous Files and Collections
Encoding Information
Encoded by Elizabeth Clarke, May 2007. Last updated by Emma Gronbeck, February 2024.
Acquisition Information
The bulk of the collection consists of transfers from the Office of Communications. Additional material has been added by various departments of the Library from multiple sources over several decades.
Series List
  A — B — C — D — E — F — G — H — I — J — K — L — M —
  N — O — P — Q — R — S — T — U — V — W — X — Y — Z
Folder List
- A
  - Ab-Am
  - An-Az
  - Abady, Isabel (Mrs. Robert), 1966-1972
  - Abbot, Gorham Dummer
  - Abbot, Richard
  - Abu-Izzeddin, Nejla Mustapha
  - Adams, James F. (trustee)
  - Adams, Nick
  - Adels, Jeffrey J.
  - Adlmann, Jan
  - Aguzzi, Danilo Lorenzo
  - Ahern, John
  - Aichele, Kathryn P.
  - Ajose, Lande
  - Akeley, Roger
  - Albers, Henry, [2 folders]
  - Alexander, Anne Stokes
  - Alexander, John Christos, 1970-1971
  - Alexander, Suzanne Spain, 1968-1974
  - Alinsky, Saul
  - Aloff, Mindy
  - Alland, Alexander, 1962-
  - Allardyce, Margaret, [2 folders]
  - Allen, Francis R. (architect of many VC buildings)
  - Allen, Helen
  - Allen, Hervey
  - Allen, John E. III
  - Allen, Mildred
  - Alley, Reuben E.
  - Allen, Walter
  - Allyn, Harriet M.
  - Almendros, Nestor
  - Aloff, Mindy (Mildred)
  - Alt, Pat
  - Alter, Martha
  - Amaru, Betsy Halpern
  - Amin, Saroia
  - Ammerman, Barbara A.
  - Amodio, Mark
  - Amosso, Meme
  - Anagnostopoulou, Irene (Miss)
  - Anderson, Dennis R.
  - Anderson, Douglas, [2 folders]
  - Anderson, Frances DeLancy
  - Anderson, Gilbert H.
  - Anderson, Jean (VC 1933)
  - Anderson, Jean Ruth
  - Anderson, Martin B. (trustee)
  - Anderson, Peter C.
  - Andersson, Laura
  - Andrews, Janet Kreuger
  - Andrews, Mark William
  - Angevine, Mark W.
  - Antelyes, Peter
  - Antolini Julia
  - Antonowicz, Ruslana M.
  - Appenzellar, Jean M., [2 folders]
  - Applebee, Constance M. K.
  - Appling, William
  - Apte, Prakash G.
  - Arbuckle, Tannis Y.
  - Arlyck, Elizabeth
  - Arlyk, Ralph, [2 folders]
  - Armstrong, Jean
  - Arnold, Irene Ringwood
  - Arthur, Jean
  - Ascheri, Carlo
  - Ashby, Philip K.
  - Ashman, Dvora
  - Askew, Pamela, [2 folders]
  - Aspinall, Catherine
  - Asprey, Winifred, [3 folders]
  - Astier, Pierre
  - Atkins, Thomas R., 1964-1965
  - Atkinson, Clinton J., Jr.
  - Attar, Malihe
  - Atwater, Edward S. (trustee)
  - Aubrey, Edwin E.
  - Austin, Genevieve H., 1963-1967
  - Austin, John, 1962-
  - Avery, Dr. Alida
  - Avery, Mary L.
  - Avery, Myra H. (sister of Georgia Avery Kendrick, VC Lady Principal)
  - Aygun, Birol
  - Azibert, Mireille
- B
  - Ba-Bar
  - Bas-Bea
  - Beh-Benn
  - Bent-Bey
  - Bic-Bol
  - Bon-Boz
  - Bra-Bru
  - Bu-By
  - Babbott, Frank L.
  - Babcock, Rufus (trustee)
  - Bach, Victor E.
  - Backus, Truman J.
  - Bacon, Helen H.
  - Bacon, Julia, [2 folders]
  - Bacon, Marion, [2 folders]
  - Badanes, Jerome
  - Baer, Catherine
  - Baer, Curtis O., 1962-1976
  - Baird, Abigail
  - Baker, Ann
  - Baker, Edgar P. (trustee)
  - Baker, Francis Ellen
  - Baker, Gladys
  - Baker, James S.
  - Balabanis, Rebecca
  - Baladon, Carlos
  - Balderrama, Sylvia
  - Baldwin, James, [2 folders]
  - Baldwin, Jane North, [2 folders]
  - Baldwin, Sherman
  - Balestri, Diane
  - Ballintine, Harriet I.
  - Balmuth, Jeremy
  - Balogh, Sara Carter (Mrs. Louis)
  - Banning, Margaret Culkin (Salsich)
  - Barach, Frederica (Pisek) (VC 1925; trustee)
  - Barber, Leila Cook, [3 folders]
  - Barbour, Violet
  - Barcham, William
  - Barenblatt, Lloyd
  - Barhite, William E.
  - Barnett, Margaret Suzanne
  - Barr, Alfred
  - Barr, Sherrie
  - Barrett, Carol Rae
  - Barron, John P.
  - Barrows, Alice
  - Bar-Sharrar, Beryl
  - Bartlett, Lynn C., [2 folders]
  - Bartlett, Margaret (Mrs. Lynn)
  - Barton, Eleanor
  - Batchelor, Howard
  - Bauer, Adelia C.
  - Bauer, Harold R.
  - Bazelow, Alexander R.
  - Beaman, Jane (Mrs. David W.)
  - Bean, Achsa, [2 folders]
  - Bean, Noel Jay
  - Bear, Kathleen C.
  - Beck, Curt W.
  - Beck, Lily
  - Beck, Rosemarie
  - Becks, Graydon F.
  - Beckvold, Ann Keith
  - Beckwith, Cora
  - Beckwith, Martha Warren, [2 folders]
  - Becraft, George E.
  - Bedell, Margaret and Mary
  - Beecher, Catherine
  - Beecher, Henry Ward
  - Beeks, Graydon F.
  - Beers, Susan
  - Begemann, Marianne
  - Behringer, Fred
  - Belknap, Mary C.
  - Belamann, Henry
  - Belding, Alice
  - Belding, Ellinor F.
  - Bell, Barbara Currier
  - Bellemore, Fred
  - Belli, Stuart L.
  - Bement, Caleb N.
  - Bendinner, Kenneth P.
  - Benedkit, Michael
  - Bennett, Ann
  - Bennett, Richard M.
  - Benenson, Harold
  - Bentley, Eileen N.
  - Berchan, Richard
  - Bereiter, Carl Edward
  - Berg, Knut
  - Berger, George K.
  - Bergeret, Ida Treat
  - Bergheim, Jeanne-Marie
  - Bergon, Frank A.
  - Bergon, Holly St. John
  - Berkley, Constance
  - Berkowe, Christiane Bresson
  - Berlow, Mark Twain
  - Berman, Susan E.
  - Bernal, Olga
  - Bernasconi, Joyce I.
  - Bernstein, Alison R.
  - Bernstein, Jane Agar
  - Bernstein, Laurie
  - Berofsky, Bernard
  - Berryhill, Michael
  - Bestor, Dorothy Koch
  - Beverly, Sharon
  - Beye, Charles Rowan
  - Bickmore, Albert S.
  - Bierman, A. K.
  - Bilginsoy, Cihan
  - Binger, Carl A. L.
  - Binger, Carl, [3 folders]
  - Birdsall, Jean
  - Birdsall, Paul
  - Bishop, Harriette (Warner) (VC 1867)
  - Bishop, Nathan
  - Bister, Ada Klett
  - Bixler, Agnes Seelye
  - Bjorklund, Elaine
  - Blackburn, Elizabeth
  - Blaker, J. Warren
  - Blanchard, Kenneth
  - Blanchard, Rita Campbell
  - Blanding, Sarah Gibson, [37 folders]
  - Blankner, Frederika
  - Blanton, Smiley
  - Blanton, Margaret Gray
  - Blau, Joseph L.
  - Blegen, Elizabeth Denny Peirce
  - Bleiberg, German, [2 folders]
  - Blier, Suzanne P.
  - Bliss, Howard
  - Bliss, Richard H.
  - Bloch, Harriet
  - Blodgett, Minnie Cumnock, [2 folders]
  - Bodel, Mrs John K., Jr.
  - Bodell, Mary Gibney
  - Bohmer, Josef
  - Bongard, Barbara R.
  - Bonime, Stephen
  - Bonner, Margo Lee
  - Bontecou, Frederic H.
  - Bonthius, Robert H., [2 folders]
  - Bonvillian, John D.
  - Booth family
  - Booth, Lydia
  - Borden, Fanny, [2 folders]
  - Boris, Brenda
  - Born, Richard J.
  - Borus, David
  - Bosman, Richard
  - Bossen, Glenda, [2 folders]
  - Bosson, Jennifer
  - Bourassa, Jonathan
  - Bouveret, Marie-Helene
  - Boveri, Marcella O’Grady
  - Bowen, Elizabeth, [2 folders]
  - Bowie, Walter Russell
  - Bowler, Alys
  - Bowman, Edward M.
  - Boyce, Robert
  - Boyd, Lola
  - Brackett, Anna C.
  - Bracq, Jean Charlemagne
  - Bradford, Carol Rothschild
  - Bradley, Carol June
  - Bradley, David
  - Brady, Robyn
  - Brain, James L.
  - Brainard, Helen
  - Braislin, Priscilla
  - Branford, Kester Adrian
  - Brann, Noel Lacy
  - Branstetter, Katherine B.
  - Braun, Robert Denton
  - Breed, Jocelyn (Harrington)
  - Brega, Louis L., [2 folders]
  - Bridge, John G.
  - Brien, Shirlyn G.
  - Briggs, Charles L.
  - Briggs, Edward
  - Brigham, Robert
  - Bright, Edward
  - Brinnin, John Malcolm
  - Briscoe, Mark
  - Brisman, Susan H
  - Broadhead, Morgan
  - Brockmeyer, Margot
  - Brodeur, Clarence A.
  - Brodsky, Jodi Ellen
  - Brokaw, Clotida A.
  - Bronson, Daniel R.
  - Brooke, Anne Calvert
  - Brooks, Fred R., Jr.
  - Brooks, H. Allen
  - Brooks, Richard A. E.
  - Broude, Gwen J.
  - Broude, Norma
  - Brouilette, Diane C.
  - Browar, Lisa M.
  - Brown, Rev. C. Victor
  - Brown, David H.
  - Brown, Donald R.
  - Brown, Emily C., [2 folders]
  - Brown, Fred E.
  - Brown, Helen M.
  - Brown, Kathleen
  - Brown, Louise Fargo
  - Brown, Michael E.
  - Brown, Robert
  - Brown, Sterling Allen [first black faculty member, see also Henrietta Smith]
  - Brownell, Elizabeth Hyde
  - Brownell, Elizabeth R.
  - Brownstein, Lewis
  - Brunger, Charles Scott
  - Bruno, Maryann
  - Brush, Helen V.
  - Brustein, Robert
  - Buch, Florence E.
  - Buchholz, Anna Odor, [3 folders]
  - Buck, Gertrude
  - Buck, Louise Bacorn
  - Buckham, Henry B.
  - Buckingham, Stephen M.
  - Budd, Donald W.
  - Bullard, Fred M.
  - Bullock, Steven
  - Bulow, Loretta
  - Bundock, Bruce
  - Bunnell, Frederick P.
  - Bunting, Charles
  - Bunting, Mary Ingraham
  - Buonfiglio, Steve
  - Burnett, Teddie S.
  - Burnham, Linda
  - Burrell, Barbara
  - Busch, Mary
  - Bush, Andrew
  - Bushnell, John H.
  - Butler, Mary
  - Butler, Mary Ann
  - Butler, Samuel Coles
  - Butler, Shirley (Oakes)
  - Butwin, Joseph
- C
  - Cab-Car
  - Cas-Caw
  - Ce-Ci
  - Cl
  - Coa-Col
  - Com-Coo
  - Cop-Coy
  - Cr-Cz
  - Cahn, Steven M.
  - Caldwell, Samuel L.
  - Campbell, John F.
  - Campbell, Kathy Ann
  - Campbell, Kenneth
  - Campbell, Leslie R.
  - Campbell, Mildred, [2 folders]
  - Cannan, Edward
  - Cao, Antonio F.
  - Carey, Jane Perry Clark, [4 folders]
  - Carlson, William R.
  - Carnes, Mark C.
  - Carol, Karen
  - Carol, Steven
  - Carpenter, Sandra
  - Carpovich, Vera (Mrs. Eugene)
  - Carroll, Eugene A.
  - Carson, Georgia (Sims)
  - Carter, Edna
  - Cartwright-Smith, Jeffrey
  - Casalis, Matthieu
  - Cassat, Paul C.
  - Cassidy, Margaret
  - Castellanos, Gloria G.
  - Catlin, Sara (Huntington)
  - Cave, Gwendolyn M.
  - Cawley, Leo C.
  - Cawley, Margaret E.
  - Cawley, William K.
  - Cazden, Norman
  - Cecil, Thomas E.
  - Celerier, Patricia-Pia
  - Celesia, Carina J.
  - Chadwick, John B.
  - Challey, Marianne Wisdom
  - Chamberlain, Barbara Blau
  - Chambers, Emily (Zimmerer)
  - Chambers, Frank P.
  - Chambers, Mortimer
  - Champlin, Terry
  - Chandler, Kenneth, [2 folders]
  - Chandler, Tina
  - Chanmugan, Dennis
  - Chapin, Jessie
  - Chapman, Dwight W., [2 folders]
  - Chapman, Elizabeth (Mrs. Dwight)
  - Chapman, Harry
  - Chapman, Shirley
  - Charity, Alan Clifford
  - Charlap, Peter
  - Charola, Asuncion Elena
  - Chasen, Gary
  - Chatterton, Clarence K., [4 folders]
  - Chaudhuri, Adhip
  - Cheetham, Ed
  - Cheng, Ying-Wan
  - Cherbonnier, Edmond La Beaume
  - Child, Eleanor Dodge
  - Chin, Yin-Lien C.
  - Chittenden, George H.
  - Chittenden, Kate S.
  - Choudhury, Mita
  - Christensen, Carol A.
  - Christenson, Richard D.
  - Christiaansen, Robert E.
  - Christie, John A., [missing as of November 2004]
  - Christmas, June (Jackson)
  - Chromey, Frederick R.
  - Chrostowski, Paul C.
  - Church, Henrietta B.
  - Church, Jennifer
  - Church, Joseph
  - Church, Monica
  - Churgin, Betty D.
  - Cikovsky, Nicolai, Jr.
  - Clark, Eleanor
  - Clark, Evalyn, [missing as of November 2004]
  - Clark, Jonathan C.
  - Clark, Patricia Ann
  - Clarke-Hazlett, Janet
  - Clarkson, David Macpherson
  - Cleveland, Linore Hobbs
  - Cleveland, Richard Folsom (trustee)
  - Cleghorn, Sarah
  - Cobb, Henry E.
  - Cochran, J. Otis
  - Cock, Elizabeth M.
  - Codere, Helen
  - Coffin, Charles A. (trustee)
  - Coffin, Elizabeth
  - Cohan, Rosamond
  - Cohen, Colleen B.
  - Cohen, Gabrielle
  - Cohen, Miriam J.
  - Cohn, Howard M.
  - Cohn, Robert Greer
  - Colander, David Charles
  - Colclough, Angela
  - Cole, Timothy
  - Coltingham, Clement
  - Colyer, Robert J.
  - Comins, Catherine
  - Conk, Margo
  - Conklin, Ruth, [2 folders]
  - Connally, G. Gordon
  - Connolly, Susan
  - Connor, Ralph
  - Conrad, Andree
  - Conrow, Georgianna
  - Consagra, Francesca
  - Constant, S. S. (trustee)
  - Constantinople, Anne P.
  - Cook, Carol J.
  - Cook, Raymond G.
  - Cool, Kenneth
  - Cooley, Leroy C.
  - Coolidge, Mary Lowell
  - Coon, Robert L.
  - Cooney, Douglas C.
  - Cooper, Jack
  - Coover, James B.
  - Copland, Susan D.
  - Corcoran, Mary Morrison (Mary B. Corcoran)
  - Cormier, Susan M.
  - Cornelius, Randolph R.
  - Cornell, Thomas (trustee)
  - Costa, Luis F.
  - Costa Neves, Jorge
  - Costello, Frank, Jr.
  - Cottingham, Clement
  - Cotton, Marion G.
  - Coulter, Cornelia Catlin
  - Counihan, Barbara Ormerod
  - Covell, Maureen Ann
  - Cowan, Carole
  - Cowell, Mary-Jean
  - Cowley, Elizabeth Buchanan
  - Cox-Byrne, Sarah E.
  - Coyle, Beverly
  - Coyler, Robert J.
  - Crabb, Cecil V., [2 folders]
  - Crabb, Harriet F.
  - Crawford, H. Marjorie, [2 folders]
  - Crimmins, Charles
  - Crosby, Howard (trustee)
  - Crothers, Diane
  - Crouch, John, [2 folders]
  - Crow, Todd
  - Crowe, Stanley John Hutchinson
  - Crowell, George
  - Cummings, Louise Duffield
  - Cowley, Elizabeth Buchanan
  - Cox-Byrne, Sarah
  - Cuno, James
  - Curie, Marie S.
  - Currier, Barbara
  - Curry, Jane E. (Leftwich)
  - Curtis, Ellen C.
  - Curtis, Frederick (trustee)
  - Cushing, Florence M., [2 folders]
  - Czin, Felicia Tedeschi
  - Czula, Roman
- D
  - Da
  - De
  - Di-Do
  - Dr-Dz
  - Dabney, Lewis M.
  - Dacre, Kathleen
  - da Cunha, Carlos E. J.
  - Dahl, Ziva E.
  - Dahlberg, Marta
  - Dalle Vacche, Angela
  - Damrosch, Walter
  - Danhert, Stephen
  - Daniels, Elizabeth Adams
  - Daniels, Jonathan (trustee)
  - Darby, Fredryc R.
  - Darensbourg, Marcetta York
  - Darlington, Beth
  - Darrach, William
  - Davenport, Frances Gardiner
  - Davis, Albert J.
  - Davis, Angela
  - Davis, Ann
  - Davis, Helen E.
  - Davis, J. Lionberger (trustee)
  - Davis, Katharine Bement (trustee), [5 folders]
  - Davis, Mary Capen
  - Davis, Philip
  - Davis, Susan
  - Davis, Theresa (Terry)
  - Davis, William J.
  - Davison, Andrew
  - Davison, Edward
  - Day, Anna
  - Day, Edmund Ezra
  - Day, James H.
  - Day, Thomas I.
  - Dayton, Mary Lee (Lowe)
  - Dean, Catherine S.
  - Dean, Vera Micheles
  - Dean, Willard L.
  - de Bidart, Genevieve Francoise
  - de Campo, Leila
  - Dedrick, Frank L.
  - De Gilio, John
  - Degler, Carl N., [4 folders]
  - Deiters, Sister Joan A.
  - Delahoyd, Mary
  - Delany, Kirby
  - De Madariaga, Pilar
  - Demarco, Nicholas
  - De Maria, Robert, Jr.
  - Dempsey, Joanne
  - Denison, Eleanor
  - DeRachewiltz, Sizzo
  - Deschere, John M.
  - De Schweinitz, Margaret
  - Deuthchman, Iva E.
  - Deutsch, Francine M.
  - Devin, Philip Lee
  - Dewitt, Marguerite E.
  - Dewsnap, Clara
  - Dickinson, George Sherman, [3 folders]
  - Dietel, William M. (trustee)
  - Dilek, Yildirim
  - Dinnerstein, Lois
  - DiPaolo, Maria Grazia
  - Divina, Milan J.
  - Dixler, Elsa J.
  - Djaparidze, Justinia (Besharov)
  - Doan, Martha
  - Dolciani, Mary P.
  - Dole, Gertrude
  - Domandi, Agnes
  - Domandi, Ann H.
  - Domandi, Mario T., [2 folders]
  - Dooling, John F., Jr., [2 folders]
  - Dooling, Robert J.
  - Dorais, Jeanne M. C.
  - Dorsey, Janet Knapp
  - Dorsey, Susan Miller
  - Doughty, Joseph C. (trustee)
  - Doughty, Sylvia K.
  - Douthett, Doane
  - Dow, John G.
  - Dow, Sterling
  - Dowell, George B.
  - Downer, Henry E., [2 folders]
  - Downer, Katherine Cookingham
  - Dows, Tracy
  - Downing, Andrew Jackson
  - Doyle, Joan E.
  - Drake, Durant
  - Drennan, Manuel J.
  - Dreyfus, Leon R.
  - Drinkwater, Geneva
  - Driscoll, Judith (Russell) (trustee)
  - Driver, Martha
  - Driver, Tom F.
  - Drobin, Frederick, Father
  - Drouilhet, Elizabeth (Moffatt), [6 folders]
  - Druian, Peter R.
  - Dubois, Cornelius (trustee)
  - Ducharme, L. Elaine
  - Duddy, Thomas A.
  - Duggan, Dr. John Michael
  - Duggan, Stephen F.
  - Duggan, Stephen P., Jr.
  - Duke, Cathy
  - Dunkel, Paul E.
  - Dunkelbarger, Janet
  - Dunn, Leslie
  - Dutton, David
  - Dwight, William B.
  - Dydo, John J.
  - Dye, Nancy Schrom
  - Dynes, Wayne
- E
  - Ea-Ei
  - Ek-Ew
  - Eames, William A.
  - Earl, Winifred
  - Early, Alice
  - Early, James
  - Ecklund, Paul Richard
  - Eckwall, David
  - Eddy, Harrison P.
  - Edwards, Carolyn Pope
  - Edwards, Darrell
  - Edwards, Rebecca
  - Edwards, William H.
  - Egan, Patricia
  - Ehrenreich, Joan
  - Eickelberg, Paul
  - Eisenberg, Edward F.
  - Ekdahl, Janis Key
  - Elias, Deborah
  - Elko, Constance B.
  - Eller, Ruth
  - Elliot, Charles Loring
  - Elliot, L. Carroll (Angell)
  - Elliott, Elia M.
  - Ellis, Constance Dimock
  - Ellis, Ruth H.
  - Elmegreen, Debra
  - Elson, Ruth Miller
  - Elsworth, Edward
  - Ely, Achsah M.
  - Embeita, Maria
  - Emerson, Alice (Frey)
  - Emmons, Cyd
  - Ennis, Glafyra
  - Epstein, Marc
  - Erb, Kenneth L.
  - Erck, Theodore H.
  - Erck, Myrtle Soles
  - Von Erhardt – Siebold, Erika
  - Erickson, Charlotte
  - Erskine, Janet Reed
  - Etherton, Alison Mann
  - Etherton, Bud
  - Eurich, Mrs. Alvin C., [2 folders]
  - Evans, Alan B.
  - Evans, Elizabeth Cornelia
  - Evarts, Allen Wardner
- F
  - Fa
  - Fe
  - Ff-Fo
  - Fr
  - Fabozzi, Patricia
  - Fahey, Joseph J.
  - Fahlund, Christine S.
  - Fahlund, G. Gregory
  - Fahnestock, Edith
  - Fainstein, Norman
  - Fair, Ethel M.
  - Fairchild, Herman LeRoy
  - Fairservis, Walter A., Jr., [2 folders]
  - Falb, Lewis W.
  - Faletti, Heidi E.
  - Fant, Ora D.
  - Farenthold, Frances (Tarlton) (trustee)
  - Farganis, James
  - Farganis, Sondra
  - Fargis-Lancaster, Beth
  - Farr, George F., Jr.
  - Farr, Judith Banzer
  - Farrar, Charles S.
  - Faulkner, Elizabeth (Coonley) (trustee)
  - Faust, Irving M.
  - Fazeli, Rafat
  - Fellows, John Edward
  - Fenkl, Heinz Insu
  - Ferdinand, Joseph
  - Fergusson, Frances Daly, [5 folders]
  - Feroe, John
  - Ferrando, Guido
  - Ferry, Anne (Davidson)
  - Ferry, Dexter M., Jr.
  - Feuer, Lewis
  - Fiedler, Miriam Foster
  - Fierce, Milfred C.
  - Finch, Charlotte E.
  - Finch, Davis W.
  - Fincke, Lois
  - Fine, Carol Gabrielson
  - Fink, Seymour
  - Finkelpearl, Katherine Dice
  - Finkelpearl, Philip
  - Finley, Ruth E. (Mrs. Emmet)
  - Fischel, Evelyn Whitmore
  - Fischinger, Andrew J.
  - Fishbein, Michael J.
  - Fisher, Armen G.
  - Fisher, Cynthia
  - Fiske, Christabel F.
  - Fitall, Rae
  - Fite, Emerson D., [4 folders]
  - Flack, Michael J.
  - Flad, Harvey K.
  - Flad, Mary
  - Flagler, Albert (VC Farmer), 1872-1921
  - Flanagan, Hallie
  - Fleishman, Doris
  - Fleming, Harold C.
  - Flentje, Ann S.
  - Flett, Helen Hendrie
  - Flint, Catherine Bockee
  - Fluck, Betty Lippman
  - Flynn, Sean
  - Fluck, Betty Lippman
  - Folger, Emily (Jordan), [2 folders]
  - Folsom, Joseph K., [4 folders]
  - Foote, Barbara (Austin) (trustee)
  - Ford, Barbara Brennan
  - Forester, David E.
  - Forman, Alice
  - Fortna, Evelyn N. C.
  - Fortna, Robert T.
  - Foshay, Ella Milbank
  - Foster, Donald
  - Foster, Frances A.
  - Foster, Tamara Rose
  - Fountain, Susan
  - Fourny, Jean-Francois
  - Fox, E. Inman
  - Fox, Helen (Morgenthau)
  - Fraher, Michael
  - Francendese, Albert A.
  - Frankel, Charles
  - Franklin, Margery Bodansky
  - Franklin, Raymond D.
  - Franklin, Susan B.
  - Franks, Lucinda
  - Fransblau, Deborah
  - Frazer, Alfred K.
  - Freedman, Frederick
  - Freedman, Mervin B.
  - Freidel, Frank
  - Fricker, Stephanie
  - Friedman, Karen L.
  - Friedman, Leslie J.
  - Friedman, Maurice
  - Friedman, Natalie
  - Frisna, Anthony
  - Fritz, Robert S.
  - Froelich, Ralph
  - Froelicher, Hans, Jr.
  - Frost, Elizabeth
  - Frost, Jerry W.
  - Frost, Robert
  - Fullerton, Helen Jane
  - Furness, Caroline E., [2 folders]
  - Furnival, Eleanor K.
  - Fusco, Miles Jr.
- G
  - Ga
  - Ge-Gh
  - Gi
  - Gl-Go
  - Gra-Gri
  - Gro-Gz
  - Gaines, Billie (Davis) (trustee)
  - Gale, Ronald M.
  - Gallagher, Merellyn
  - Gallo, Paul
  - Gallon, Robert L.
  - Gambino, Ellen M.
  - Garcia Lorca, Federico
  - Garcia-Renart, Luis
  - Garnsey, Gertrude G., [2 folders]
  - Garnett, Wendell D.
  - Garvey, Mary Katherine
  - Gasman, Lydia
  - Gay, Dorothy Ann
  - Geehr, Jeane Humphreys
  - Geer, E. Harold, [2 folders]
  - Gehret, G. Michael, 1970-1974
  - Geiger, Elisabeth De Chamisso
  - Geiger, Moritz A.
  - Geist, Sidney
  - Gekler, R. Brooks
  - Gellert, Betsy
  - Gellman, Lola
  - Gensheimen, C.
  - George, Jean
  - George, John L.
  - George, Richard N., Jr.
  - Gephart, William
  - Geraci, Angela
  - Gerber, Robert Ira
  - Gerzina, Gretchen
  - Gezek, Mary (Mrs. Thaddeus)
  - Gesek, Thaddeus Joseph, [2 folders]
  - Getman, Susan Dixon
  - Getter, Karen
  - Gevalt, Ruth V.
  - Giannini, Daniel
  - Gibbons, Mary Weitzel
  - Gibson, Evelyn
  - Giffin, Mary Elizabeth
  - Gifford, Alice H.
  - Gifford, Virginia S.
  - Gifford, William W.
  - Gilbert, Mary Jordan
  - Gilinski, Alberta Steinman
  - Gilkeson, Elizabeth C.
  - Gilkey, Langdon B.
  - Gillen, Ann
  - Gillespie, Betty Jean
  - Gillin, Donald G.
  - Gillotti, Susan McCabe
  - Gilmartin, Kristine
  - Gilroy, Mary Lou
  - Giraud, Jacob P., Jr., [2 folders]
  - Gittleman, Anne Iker, [2 folders]
  - Glasse, John H.
  - Glasse, Mrs. John (Lou)
  - Glassman, Milton R.
  - Gleason, Josephine M., [3 folders]
  - Glennan, T. Keith
  - Godfrey, Brian
  - Godwin, Gail
  - Goldensohn, Lorrie
  - Goldin, Harrison J.
  - Goldman, Arnold Melvyn
  - Goldring, Louis
  - Goldsmith, Cornelia
  - Goldstein, Anne L.
  - Goldstein, Judith
  - Goldstein, Mildred
  - Gooding, Frederic Jr.
  - Gooding, Velma
  - Goodman, Sherry L.
  - Goodrich, Herbert F.
  - Goodsell, Abby F.
  - Goodwin, Abby M.
  - Gordan, Esther
  - Gordon, Bethann
  - Gordon, Joan
  - Gordon, Linda Winkelhaus
  - Goss, Doris
  - Goss, Jennifer
  - Goss, Tania
  - Goudy, Frances L.
  - Gould, Miriam C.
  - Gounaris, Anne D.
  - Gourevitch, Jacqueline
  - Goven, Beverly A.
  - Gow, George Coleman
  - Grabowska, Flora
  - Grabowski, Chris
  - Grady, Donna
  - Graham, Claire D.
  - Graham, Wendy
  - Grauman, Lawrence, Jr.
  - Gray, Janet
  - Gray, Obika (Errol)
  - Gregg, Richard A.
  - Green, Annie
  - Green, Douglas S.
  - Green, Howard L.
  - Green, Sondra
  - Green, Warren Ida
  - Green, William Baillie
  - Greenberg, Yvonne Roeder
  - Greenbie, Marjorie Barstow
  - Greene, Marcia
  - Greenough, Ruth Horblower (trustee)
  - Greenwood, Marci (Dr. M.R.C.), [2 folders]
  - Gregg, Richard A.
  - Gregory, Sarita
  - Greifer, Elisha
  - Greig, Melissa
  - Grene, Majorie
  - Grennan, Eamon
  - Grennan, Joan
  - Griffen, Clyde, [2 folders]
  - Griffin, Carroll W.
  - Griffin, Charles C., [4 folders]
  - Griffen, Sarah D.
  - Griffith, Agnes E.
  - Griffith, Sally F.
  - Griggs, John C.
  - Griliknes, Nancy
  - Grilli, Renata
  - Gross, Mason
  - Groth, Janet
  - Grover, Elizabeth L.
  - Groves, Earl
  - Gualtieri, Antonio R.
  - Guernsey, Raymond G.
  - Guichard, David
  - Guion, Connie
  - Gunther, Trude
  - Guthrie, Belinda
  - Gutman, Helmut J.
- H
  - Haa-Han
  - Har-Haz
  - He-Hi
  - Ho
  - Hs-Hz
  - Haas, Stephen
  - Haddad, Yvonne
  - Hadley, Helen Morris